(Leonard:)What's up
with the infrared cameras?
(Sheldon:)I'm measuring residual heat
levels on the playing cards
(Sheldon:)to determine
which one's been touched.
(Sheldon:)By the way,
(Sheldon:)if you hope to have children,
(Sheldon:)I suggest you switch
from briefs to boxers.
(Sheldon:)Your testicles look a tad warm.
(Leonard:)Holy crap,
are you connected
(Leonard:)to the Oak Ridge
National Laboratory?
(Sheldon:)Yes. I'm using their
Cray supercomputer
(Sheldon:)to analyze
shuffling patterns.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, that computer
is used
for national defense.
(Leonard:)Hacking into it is
a federal crime.
(Sheldon:)Relax, we're not under
attack right now.
(Leonard:)Okay, I'm leaving before the
black helicopters get here.
(Sheldon:)And is this my card?
(Sheldon:)Rats!
(Sheldon:)I wonder if Howard used
a radioactive tracer.